Lawrence Colton Anderson

(801) 941-5161

Email: Anderson0741@icloud.com

Github: Anderson0741

Portfolio Site: anderson0741.space

903 E Carnation Dr Sandy, UT 84094

Web Developer with a background in sales and client relations creating hundreds of accounts over a 5 year period and maintaining one of the company's highest retention rates. Looking to apply recent training in front end development including JavaScript and React. Eager to learn new programming languages.

SKILLS

F	r	0	'n	t-	Е	n	d
---	---	---	----	----	---	---	---

- JavaScript
- React
- HTML/CSS

Back-End

- NodeJS
- Express
- Mongoose
- MongoDB

Other Skills

- Git
- JSON
- Sales
- Customer Service

GITHUB WORK

level_up_auto

This Website for Level Up Auto was built with React, and is a fully CRUD application. I added user authentication so administrators can add posts, edit posts, and delete posts. For the CSS I used flexbox, and used flex grid to align the content that I wanted in certain places and sizes.

EXPERIENCE

Polished Image, Layton Utah - Detailing Technician

April 2011 - January 2012

- Thoroughly cleaned cars
- Picked up and delivered vehicles

Vivint, Texas - Sales Representative | Product Service Consultant

March 2012 - 2014 / 2015 - 2017

- Installed home and business security systems
- Consulted home and business owners on their systems
- Set up the new accounts

Fuse Satellite, Nashville Tennessee - Sales Representative

May 2014 - October 2014

- Set up alternative TV services to save customers money
- Explained what they would get with Directv/Dish
- Trained new sales representatives

EDUCATION

V School, Salt Lake City Utah - Web Development | Full Stack Javascript Developer 2017 - 2018

Utah Valley University, Orem Utah - International Business I Personal Finance

January 2012 - 2016

Weber State University, Ogden Utah - Associate's Degree

August 2008 - December 2009

Part of the New Century Program